Board of Governors fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Policies and procedures, 1965 - 2003; F-33-3; 83 cm of textual records
  - Academic policies (A series), 1992 - 2003; F-33-3-5; 6 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of A series policies and their revisions over time.
    - Academic policies and procedures - table of contents, 1992 - 1996; F-33-3-5-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-171.
    - A 10.01 Academic appointments, 1994 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-172.
    - A 10.02 Technical appointments procedures, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-215.
    - A 10.03 Endowed academic appointments, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-173.
    - A 10.04 Hiring of foreign faculty members, 1992 - 2002; F-33-3-5-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-206.
    - A 10.05 Summary of employment and immigration procedures, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-207.
    - A 10.06 Appointment of specially funded university chairs, 2000; F-33-3-5-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.01 Renewal, tenure and promotion, 1992 - 1996; F-33-3-5-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-174.
    - A 11.01 Tenure track appointments, 2003; F-33-3-5-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.02 Criteria for appointment, promotion, contract renewal, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-175.
    - A 11.02 Promotions policy, 2003; F-33-3-5-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.03 Joint appointments, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.03 Renewal, tenure and promotion procedures, 2003; F-33-3-5-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.04 Appointment of part-time faculty, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-176.
    - A. 11.04 Tenure, promotion, faculty review cttes., 2003; F-33-3-5-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.05 Modification of faculty appointments, 1992 - 1995; F-33-3-5-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-177.
    - A 11.05 Criteria for appointment, contract renewal, 2003; F-33-3-5-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 11.06 Tenure and promotion appeals, 2003; F-33-3-5-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 12.01 Lecturers and senior lecturers, 1992 - 1995; F-33-3-5-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-178.
    - A 12.01 Teaching appointments, 2000; F-33-3-5-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 12.02 Laboratory instructors I and II, 1992 - 1995; F-33-3-5-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-179.
    - A 12.03 Librarians, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-180.
    - A 12.04 Visiting faculty, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 12.05 Limited Term Faculty, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-181.
    - A 12.06 Faculty associates and program coordinators, 1992 - 1998; F-33-3-5-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-182.
    - A 12.07 Associate members, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 12.08 Adjunct professors, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 12.09 Sessional lecturers, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-183.
    - A 12.10 Appointment of retired faculty, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-223.
    - A 12.11 Professors emeriti/ae, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 12.12 Inservice associates, 1998; F-33-3-5-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 13.01 Academic administrative appointments, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 13.02 Appointment of department chairs, 1992 - 1996; F-33-3-5-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 13.03 Appointment of associate deans, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 13.04 Terms of appointment for dept. chairs, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-184.
    - A 13.05 Search committees for deans, 1992 - 1998; F-33-3-5-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-185.
    - A 13.06 Responsibilities of deans, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 13.07 Terms of appointment - deans, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 20.01 Faculty salaries, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-216.
    - A 20.02 Academic salary scales, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-186.
    - A 21.01 Benefits for SFUFA bargaining unit members, retirees and visiting faculty, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-187.
    - A 21.02 Relocation expenses for tenure track faulty, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-42 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-188.
    - A 21.03 Mortgage assistance program, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-43 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-189.
    - A 21.04 Professional development allowance for members of SFUFA bargaining unit, 1994 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-44 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-190.
    - A 21.05 Tuition waiver policy, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-45 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-191.
    - A 21.06 Enhanced early retirement policy, 1993 - 1997; F-33-3-5-0-46 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-192.
    - A 30.01 Code of faculty ethics and responsibilities, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-47 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 30.02 Trimester operation, 1992 - 1995; F-33-3-5-0-48 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-193.
    - A 30.03 Tenure-track faculty workload, 1992 - 1998; F-33-3-5-0-49 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-194.
    - A 30.04 Disclosure and approval of outside activities, 1992 - 1999; F-33-3-5-0-50 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-220.
    - A 30.05 Strike policy, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-51 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 30.06 Resignations - faculty members, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-52 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 30.07 Retirement date - faculty members, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-53 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 30.08 Release of equipment when faculty leave SFU, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-54 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 30.09 Disciplinary measures, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-55 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-217.
    - A 31.01 Leave of absense, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-56 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 31.02 Study leave, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-57 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-195.
    - A 31.03 Sick leave and long term disability, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-58 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 31.04 Faculty exchanges, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-59 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 31.05 Maternity, adoption, and parental leave, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-5-0-60 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-196.
    - A 31.06 Study leave for lecturers,senior lecturers, instructors, librarians, and archivists, 2000 - 2002; F-33-3-5-0-61 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 32.01 Award for excellence in teaching, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-5-0-62 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-218.
    - A 32.02 University professor, university research proessor, 1992; F-33-3-5-0-63 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
    - A 40.01 Centres and institutes, 1992 - 1997; F-33-3-5-0-64 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-197.
    - Senate Procedures, 1992 - 1994; F-33-3-5-0-65 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-203.
    - SFUFA Framework, 1992 - 1995; F-33-3-5-0-66 (Archival box - standard 33-79)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-204.
  - Research policies (R series), 1992 - 2003; F-33-3-6; 3 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of R series policies and their revisions over time.
    - R 10.01 External research grants and contracts, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 10.02 Research semester research grant, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 10.03 Sabbatical leave research grant, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-221.
    - R 20.01 Ethics review of research involving human subjects, 1992 - 2002; F-33-3-6-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 20.02 Biosafety committee, 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-6-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-222.
    - R 20.03 Treatment of animals in research and teaching, 1992 - 2001; F-33-3-6-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-219.
    - R 20.04 Radiological safety, 1997; F-33-3-6-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 20.05 Non-ionizing radiation safety, 2003; F-33-3-6-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 30.01 Copyright policy, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 30.02 Patent policy, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-198.
    - R 40.01 Centres and institutes, 1997; F-33-3-6-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 50.01 University research associate, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 50.02 Employment of personnel funded from research grants and contracts, 1992; F-33-3-6-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - 50.03 Postdoctoral fellows policy, 2000; F-33-3-6-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - R 60.01 Integrity in research and misconduct in research, 1995; F-33-3-6-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
  - Teaching policies (T series), 1992 - 2000; F-33-3-7; 1 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of T series policies and their revisions over time.
    - T 10.01 Code of student conduct, 1994 - 2000; F-33-3-7-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-199.
    - T 10.02 Code of academic honesty, 1994 - 2000; F-33-3-7-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-200.
    - T 10.03 University board on student discipline (UBSD), 1994 - 2000; F-33-3-7-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-201.
    - T 10.04 Senate committee on disciplinary appeals (SCODA) - Terms of reference, 1995 - 1998; F-33-3-7-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-202.
    - T 20.01 Grading practices and grade appeals, 1992; F-33-3-7-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
    - T 20.02 Final examinations, 1992; F-33-3-7-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-88)
  - Administrative policies (AD series), 1969 - 2003; F-33-3-8; 11 cm of textual records
    Subseries consists of AD series policies and their revisions over time.
    - AD Series policy list, 1972 - 1995; F-33-3-8-0-1 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-57.
    - Administrative policy and procedures instruction, 1969; F-33-3-8-0-2 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-58.
    - AD 1-1 Central Stores requisitioning, 1969 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-3 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives:.
    - AD 1-2 Displaying of flags, 1969 - 1982; F-33-3-8-0-4 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-60.
    - AD 1-3 Traffic and parking regulations, 1969 - 1996; F-33-3-8-0-5 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-61.
    - AD 1-4 Control of keys, 1973 - 1993; F-33-3-8-0-6 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-62.
    - AD 1-5 Long distance telephone charges, 1969 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-7 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-63.
    - AD 1-6 Commercial outlets, advertising and selling on campus, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-8 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-64.
    - AD 1-7 Use of university facilities by the university community, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-9 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-65.
    - AD 1-8 Use of university facilities by off-campus organizations, 1975 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-10 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-66.
    - AD 1-9 Furniture, 1969 - 1993; F-33-3-8-0-11 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-67.
    - AD 1-10 Lost property, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-12 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-68.
    - AD 1-11 Maintenance and repair of office machines, 1969 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-13 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-69.
    - AD 1-12 Serving of alcoholic beverages at campus functions, 1970 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-14 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-70.
    - AD 1-13 Fire policy, 1972 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-15 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-71.
    - AD 1-14 Control of university motor vehicles, 1972 - 1981; F-33-3-8-0-16 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-72.
    - AD 1-15 Telephone service, 1974 - 1989; F-33-3-8-0-17 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-73.
    - AD 1-16 Office photocopying policy, 1975 - 1981; F-33-3-8-0-18 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-74.
    - AD 1-17 Control and scheduling of athletic facilities, 1975 - 1979; F-33-3-8-0-19 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-75.
    - AD 1-18 Display of notices, posters, advertisements, etc. on campus, 1981 - 1984; F-33-3-8-0-20 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-76.
    - AD 3-1 Petty cash, 1969 - 1997; F-33-3-8-0-21 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-77.
    - AD 3-2 Travel and business expenses, 1974 - 2003; F-33-3-8-0-22 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-78.
    - AD 3-3 Direct acquisition of goods and services, 1970; F-33-3-8-0-23 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-79.
    - AD 3-4 Chart of accounts - operating, 1975 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-24 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-80.
    - AD 3-5 Credit and collection, 1972; F-33-3-8-0-25 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-81.
    - AD 3-6 Rental of vehicles, 1973; F-33-3-8-0-26 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-82.
    - AD 3-7 Travel accident insurance, 1974; F-33-3-8-0-27 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-83.
    - AD 3-8 Donations from faculty and staff, 1984; F-33-3-8-0-28 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-84.
    - AD 3-9 Directed and foregone payments for university purposes, 1984; F-33-3-8-0-29 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-85.
    - AD 3-10 Internal audit policy, 1986; F-33-3-8-0-30 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-86.
    - AD 3-11 Employee/independent contractor policy, 1992 - 1997; F-33-3-8-0-31 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-87.
    - AD 3-12 Supplementary course fees, 1995; F-33-3-8-0-32 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 3-13 Service contracts, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-33 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 3-14 Indemnity approval policy, 2000; F-33-3-8-0-34 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 3-15 Investment management operating procedures, 2003; F-33-3-8-0-35 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 5-1 Acquisition of computer equipment, 1970 - 1984; F-33-3-8-0-36 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-88.
    - AD 5-2 Sale of computing services to non SFU organizations, 1972 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-37 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-89.
    - AD 5-3 Request for Computing Centre services, 1972; F-33-3-8-0-38 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-90.
    - AD 5-4 System development, 1972 - 1979; F-33-3-8-0-39 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-91.
    - AD 7-1 Repair of audio visual equipment, 1969 - 1980; F-33-3-8-0-40 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-92.
    - AD 9-1 Personnel employment policies, 1977 - 1992; F-33-3-8-0-41 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-93.
    - AD 9-2 Establishment of positions, 1976 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-42 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-94.
    - AD 9-3 Filling of positions, 1977 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-43 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-95.
    - AD 9-4 Modification of appointments from full-time to part time, 1976 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-44 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-96.
    - AD 9-5 Job splits, 1976 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-45 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-97.
    - AD 9-6 Salary administration, 1976 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-46 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-98.
    - AD 9-7 Group benefit plans, 1990 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-47 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-99.
    - AD 9-8 Leaves (with or without pay), 1976 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-48 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-100.
    - AD 9-9 Training and development, 1977 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-49 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-101.
    - AD 9-10 Tuition waiver, 1981 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-50 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-102.
    - AD 9-11 Study leave, 1981 - 1993; F-33-3-8-0-51 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-103.
    - AD 9-12 Business travel protection, 1990; F-33-3-8-0-52 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-104.
    - AD 9-13 Working conditions, 1982 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-53 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-105.
    - AD 9-14 No discrimination, 1982 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-54 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-106.
    - AD 9-15 Strike policy, 1984 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-55 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-107.
    - AD 9-16 Performance appraisal, 1985 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-56 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-108.
    - AD 9-17 Problem solving, 1976 - 1990; F-33-3-8-0-57 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-109.
    - AD 9-18 Occupational continuity, 1990 - 1994; F-33-3-8-0-58 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-110.
    - AD 9-19 Discipline and termination, 1990; F-33-3-8-0-59 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-111.
    - AD 9-20 Resignation, 1990; F-33-3-8-0-60 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-112.
    - AD 9-21 Retirement, 1990; F-33-3-8-0-61 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-113.
    - AD 9-22 Professional development, 1993 - 1996; F-33-3-8-0-62 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-114.
    - AD 9-23 Rehabilitative employment, 1973; F-33-3-8-0-63 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-115.
    - AD 9-24 Employment of personnel funded from external grants, 1974; F-33-3-8-0-64 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-116.
    - AD 10.1 Employment policies, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-65 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
    - AD 10.2 Establishment of positions, 1999 - 2000; F-33-3-8-0-66 (Archival box - standard 33-78)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-33-3-3-0-208.
    - AD 10.3 Posting and filling of positions, 1999; F-33-3-8-0-67 (Archival box - standard 33-78)